# ADAM **DONNER**



(402) 699.6819



adamdonner@gmail.com



15415 Tucker Street Bennington, NE 68007

# **SKILLS**

Direct Sales Project Management **Product Marketing** Sales Operations New Business Development B2B Sales **Channel Management** Cold Calling Account Management CMR, Salesforce.com Digital Print Technology Sales

# **EDUCATION**

# **UNIVERSITY OF NEBRASKA**

Lincoln, NE **BS-Management** May 2003

**CDIA+** Certification DocuWare Technical Certification eCopy Technical Certification

#### **PROFILE**

Results orientated professional with 15+ years of sales and project management experience in a technology-focused environment. A strong communicator with exceptional skills in developing customer relationships. Demonstrated initiative and dedication to success. Demonstrated outside sales, cold-calling and relationship building skills. Proven ability to effectively overcome obstacles and adversity in a competitive marketplace.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **DIRECTOR OF SALES & MARKETING**

Digital Express | February 2016-November 2018

- Responsible for key account management
- Manage daily sales and activities inside of Digital Express
- Build customer websites using Digital Store Front and other CMS
- Develop timelines for deployment, set milestones for each stage of development from conception to delivery

# **REGIONAL SALES MANAGER**

Nuance Communications | February 2011-February 2016

- Drove and managed Nuance software sales with channel partners and end user customers
- Coordinated and provided training to sales/strategic teams on positioning the solutions provided by Nuance Communications
- Managed the sales and implementation process for mid to large opportunities across the territory
- Worked with 'C' level management in a consultative sales approach to develop solutions that enhanced the organizations' business processes
- Consistent history of exceeding quarterly and yearly revenue targets (Chairman's Club 2011, 2012, 2013)

# **REGIONAL SOLUTIONS CONSULTANT**

Konica Minolta Business Solutions | April 2006-February 2011

- Managed regional sales & implementation of software and Optimized Print Service (OPS) business
- Coordinated and provided training to sales team
- Preformed all activities in OPS sales process-opportunity development, sales presentations, data acquisition, proposal development
- Worked with internal resources as well as third party vendors to coordinate project activities